A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Speeches, Series 33 FA372
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Temple Emanu-El Testimonial Dinner - New York City, December 16, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 2621)
- Nixon Victory Dinner - Erie County Republican Committee - Buffalo, New York, December 19, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 2622)
- Nixon Victory Dinner - Erie County Republican Committee - Buffalo, New York, December 19, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 2623)
- Gabe Pressman Interview - New York City, December 20, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 2624)
- Health, Education and Welfare - New York City, December 23, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 2625)
  NAR testifies on Medicaid before Health, Education & Welfare.
- Health, Education and Welfare - New York City, December 23, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 2626)
- New York State Supreme Court - New York City, January 2, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2627)
  Swearing-in ceremony of 17 judges.
- New York State Supreme Court - New York City, January 2, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2628)
- NAR Annual Message to the Legislature 1969, January 8, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2629)
- NAR Annual Message to the Legislature 1969, January 8, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2630)
- NAR Annual Message to the Legislature 1969, January 8, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2631)
- National Aeronautics Space Administration - New York City, January 10, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2632)
  Dinner honoring Apollo 8 astronauts.
- National Aeronautics Space Administration - New York City, January 10, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2633)
- New York State Federation of Women's Republican Clubs - New York City, January 10, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2634)
- Reception for Lyndon Baines Johnson - New York City, January 13, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2635)
- Reception for Lyndon Baines Johnson - New York City, January 13, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2636)
- New York State Women's Joint Legislative Forum - Albany, New York, January 14, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2637)
- New York State Women's Joint Legislative Forum - Albany, New York, January 14, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2638)
- New York State Broadcasters Association - New York City, January 15, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2639)
- New York State Agricultural Society - Syracuse, New York, January 16, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2640)
- NAR Budget Message to Legislature - Albany, New York, January 21, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2641)
- Governor's Club Dinner - New York City, January 22, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2642)
- Governor's Club Dinner - New York City, January 22, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2643)
- Narcotic Addiction Control Commission - New York City, January 23, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2644)
  Film premiere of "Three."
- Narcotic Addiction Control Commission - New York City, January 23, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2645)
- National Women's Republican Club - New York City, January 25, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2646)
  Delivered by Secretary of State Lomenzo.
- National Women's Republican Club - New York City, January 25, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2647)
- Alfalfa Dinner - Washington, DC, January 25, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2648)
- USO - New York City, January 26, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2649)
  USO presentation of 1968 Woman of the Year award to Pearl Bailey.
- USO - New York City, January 26, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2650)
- Legislative Conference of Business and Professional Women's Clubs - Albany, New York, January 27, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2651)
- Hellenic College - Spyros Skouras 75th Jubilee Dinner, January 28, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2652)
- Hellenic College - Spyros Skouras 75th Jubilee Dinner, January 28, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2653)
- Washington Post Reception - New York City, January 28, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2654)
- Endicott Johnson Corporation - Plant Dedication - Endicott, New York, January 29, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2655)
- Endicott Johnson Corporation - Plant Dedication - Endicott, New York, January 29, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2656)
- Society of Scholarship Founder's Luncheon - New York City, January 29, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2657)
- American Institute of Planners - New York Regional Conference - New York City, January 30, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2658)
- American Institute of Planners - New York Regional Conference - New York City, January 30, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2659)
- Westchester County Republican Fund Raising Dinner - New York City, January 30, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2660)
- Westchester County Republican Fund Raising Dinner - New York City, January 30, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2661)
- New York State Bar Association - New York City, January 31, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2662)
- New York State Bar Association - New York City, January 31, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2663)
- New York State Society of Newspaper Editors - Buffalo, New York, February 3, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2664)
- New York State Society of Newspaper Editors - Buffalo, New York, February 3, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2665)
- Jewish War Veterans Convention - Legislative Breakfast - Albany, New York, February 4, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2666)
- Jewish War Veterans Convention - Legislative Breakfast - Albany, New York, February 4, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2667)
- Empire State Chamber of Commerce - 19th Annual Dinner - Albany, New York, February 4, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2668)
- Empire State Chamber of Commerce - 19th Annual Dinner - Albany, New York, February 4, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2669)
- Empire State Chamber of Commerce - Luncheon with Board of Directors - Albany, New York, February 5, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2670)
- 6th Annual Legislative Assembly of the New York State Association for Mental Health - Albany, New York, February 5, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2671)
- 6th Annual Legislative Assembly of the New York State Association for Mental Health - Albany, New York, February 5, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2672)
- Republican Citizens Committee of Onondaga County - Syracuse, New York, February 6, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2673)
- Republican Citizens Committee of Onondaga County - Syracuse, New York, February 6, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2674)
- Press Conference re: Urban Development Corporation Projects - Rochester, New York - Cancelled, February 7, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2675)
- Association of Towns - Annual Meeting - New York City, February 11, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2676)
- Association of Towns - Annual Meeting - New York City, February 11, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2677)
- Association of the Fire Districts of New York State - Annual Meeting - New York City, February 11, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2678)
- Association of the Fire Districts of New York State - Annual Meeting - New York City, February 11, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2679)
- President's Council for Urban Affairs - Washington, DC, February 12, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2680)
- Abraham Lincoln Association Banquet - Springfield, Illinois, February 12, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2681)
- Abraham Lincoln Association Banquet - Springfield, Illinois, February 12, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2682)
- Wharton School of Finance of the University of Pennsylvania - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, February 13, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2683)
- Wharton School of Finance of the University of Pennsylvania - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, February 13, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2684)
- New York County Republican Committee Lincoln Day Dinner - New York City, February 15, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2685)
- New York County Republican Committee Lincoln Day Dinner - New York City, February 15, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2686)
- Albany County Republican Committee Lincoln Day Dinner - Albany, New York, February 17, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2687)
- Albany County Republican Committee Lincoln Day Dinner - Albany, New York, February 17, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2688)
- Latin American Statement, February 17, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2689)
  Governor accepts mission.
- American Society for Public Administration - Washington, DC, February 19, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2690)
- American Society for Public Administration - Washington, DC, February 19, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2691)
- National Governors' Conference - Washington, DC, February 26-27, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2692)
- League of Women Voters Conference - Albany, New York, March 4, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2692A)
- Governor's Conference on the Future of Transportation in New York State - New York City, March 3-4, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2693)
- League of Women Voters Conference - Albany, New York, March 4, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2694)
- Press Conference re: New York City - Mayor Lindsay, March 4, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2695)
- Colgate University - 150th Anniversary Convocation - Hamilton, New York, March 5, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2696)
- Colgate University - 150th Anniversary Convocation - Hamilton, New York, March 5, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2697)
- Commerce and Industry Association Luncheon - New York City, March 6, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2698)
- Commerce and Industry Association Luncheon - New York City, March 6, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2699)
- Statement Before Sub-Committee on Economic Development of the Senate Committee on Public Works, March 7, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2700)
  Delivered by Charles Lanigan.
- Legislative Correspondents Association Dinner - Albany, New York, March 8, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2701)
- Legislative Correspondents Association Dinner - Albany, New York, March 8, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2702)
- New York State Broadcasters Association Dinner - Albany, New York, March 11, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2703)
- New York State Broadcasters Association Dinner - Albany, New York, March 11, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2704)
- IBM Public Affairs Council - Albany, New York, March 13, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2705)
- Statement re: Nixon and Anti-Ballistic Missiles, March 14, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2706)
- National Alliance of Businessmen - Washington, DC, March 15, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2707)
- National Alliance of Businessmen - Washington, DC, March 15, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2708)
- Gridiron Club Dinner - Washington, DC, March 15, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2709)
- Gridiron Club Dinner - Washington, DC, March 15, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2710)
- Friendly Sons of St. Patrick - 185th Anniversary Dinner - New York City, March 17, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2711)
- Friendly Sons of St. Patrick - 185th Anniversary Dinner - New York City, March 17, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2712)
- Lindsay Announcement re: Mayoralty - Gracie Mansion, New York City, March 18, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2713)
- United Jewish Appeal - New York City, March 20, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2714)
- United Jewish Appeal - New York City, March 20, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2715)
- Urban Development Corporation Announcement - Buffalo, New York, March 21, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2716)
- Lunch Presentation - Planning for Impact, State University of New York Buffalo - Buffalo, New York, March 21, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2717)
- Presentation of Buffalo/Amherst Corridor Study - Williamsville, New York, March 21, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2718)
- Inner Circle Dinner - New York City, March 22, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2719)
- Tribute to Dr. Allen - Albany, New York, March 22, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2720)
- New York State Publishers Association, Inc. - Albany, New York, March 22, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2721)
- New York State Publishers Association, Inc. - Albany, New York, March 22, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2722)
- Rockland County Republican Committee Breakfast - New City, New York, March 28, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2723)
- Rockland County Republican Committee Breakfast - New City, New York, March 28, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2724)
- Committee on Appalachia Statement - Washington, DC, March 31, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2725)
- Delaware River Basin Authority - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, April 10, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2726)
- Delaware River Basin Authority - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, April 10, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2727)
- Pan American Union - Washington, DC, April 14, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2728)
- Pan American Day - Organization of American States - Washington, DC, April 14, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2729)
- Reception for Dr. Allen - Albany, New York, April 14, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2730)
- Press Conference with Mayor Lindsay - Battery Park City, New York City, April 16, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2731)
- Press Conference with Mayor Lindsay - Battery Park City, New York City, April 16, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2732)
- Building Trades Employers Association - Annual Dinner - New York City, April 17, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2733)
- Building Trades Employers Association - Annual Dinner - New York City, April 17, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2734)
- WCBS-TV "Newsmaker" Show Taping - New York City, April 19, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2735)
- WCBS-TV "Newsmaker" Show Taping - New York City, April 19, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2736)
- Meeting with Directors of the Associated Press - New York City, April 20, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2737)
- Niagara Falls Chamber of Commerce - Niagara Falls, New York, April 21, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2738)
- Niagara Falls Chamber of Commerce - Niagara Falls, New York, April 21, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2739)
- Turbo Train Arrival - Rensselaer, New York, April 21, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2740)
- Interracial Council for Business Opportunity, April 23, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2741)
- Interracial Council for Business Opportunity, April 23, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2742)
- Dinner for Dr. Allen - Albany, New York, April 24, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2743)
- Republican Governors' Association - Lexington, Kentucky, April 20-May 3, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2744)
- 8th Annual Governor's Conference on the Aging - New York City, May 2, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2745)
  Attorney General Louis J. Lefkowitz delivers the Governor's speech.
- 8th Annual Governor's Conference on the Aging - New York City, May 2, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2746)
- Beth Israel Hospital - 80th Anniversary Dinner - New York City, May 4, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2747)
- A. Philip Randolph 80th Birthday Dinner - New York City, May 6, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2748)
- A. Philip Randolph 80th Birthday Dinner - New York City, May 6, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2749)
- St. Patrick's Cathedral - New York City, May 7, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2750)
  Mass upon Cardinal Cooke's return from Rome.
- St. Patrick's Cathedral - New York City, May 7, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2751)
- Governor's Committee on Scholastic Achievement - New York City, May 7, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2752)
  14th Annual Senator Wagner Memorial Dinner.
- Governor's Committee on Scholastic Achievement - New York City, May 7, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2753)
- American Institute of Architects - Annual Dinner - New York City, May 7, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2754)
- American Institute of Architects - Annual Dinner - New York City, May 7, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2755)
- Metropolitan Museum of Art - New York City, May 8, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2756)
  Preview of NAR's Primitive Art Exhibit "Art of Oceania, Africa & and the Americas."
- Metropolitan Museum of Art - New York City, May 8, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2757)
- B'nai B'rith - 11th Annual Youth Services Dinner, May 8, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2758)
  Honoring Lester Avnet.
- B'nai B'rith - 11th Annual Youth Services Dinner, May 8, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2759)
- New York State Council on the Arts, May 8, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2760)
- Joint Labor-Management Committee of the Building and Construction Trades Luncheon - New York City, May 20, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2761)
- Joint Labor-Management Committee of the Building and Construction Trades Luncheon - New York City, May 20, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2762)
- Museum of Primitive Art - New York City, May 20, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2763)
  Opening of NAR Mexican Folk Art Exhibit
- New York Bank for Savings - 150th Anniversary Luncheon, May 22, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2764)
- New York Bank for Savings - 150th Anniversary Luncheon, May 22, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2765)
- Caribbean Festival - New York City - Cancelled, May 23, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2766)
- Caribbean Festival - New York City - Cancelled, May 23, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2767)
- American Management Association - 2nd Annual Mobilization for Urban Action Conference - New York City, May 26, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2767A)
- American Management Association - 2nd Annual Mobilization for Urban Action Conference - New York City, May 26, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2768)
- Museum of Modern Art - "20th Century Art from NAR Collection" Exhibit - New York City, May 26, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2769)
- Museum of Modern Art - "20th Century Art from NAR Collection" Exhibit - New York City, May 26, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2770)
- Citizens Committee on the Problems of Alcohol - New York City, May 28, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2771)
  Delivered by Lt. Governor Wilson.
- Marymount College Commencement - Tarrytown, New York, June 1, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2772)
- New York Republican State Committee - 21st Annual Dinner - New York City, June 5, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2773)
- New York Republican State Committee - 21st Annual Dinner - New York City, June 5, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2774)
- President's Commission on Income Maintenance Program, June 7, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2775)
  George K. Wyman delivers speech for Governor.
- President's Commission on Income Maintenance Program, June 7, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2776)
- House Subcommittee on Intergovernmental Relations - Washington, DC, June 10, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2777)
  NAR testimony on Intergovernmental Cooperation Act.
- United Jewish Appeal - New York City, June 12, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2779)
  Person-to-Person telephone meeting.
- Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute - Commencement Exercises - Troy, New York, June 13, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2780)
- Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute - Commencement Exercises - Troy, New York, June 13, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2781)
- Dartmouth College - Commencement Exercises - Hanover, New Hampshire, June 15, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2782)
- Dartmouth College - Commencement Exercises - Hanover, New Hampshire, June 15, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2783)
- Hudson River Valley Water Pollution Enforcement Conference - New York City, June 18, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2784)
  State Health Commissioner Hollis S. Ingraham delivers the Governor's speech.
- United Jewish Appeal Lunch - Herbert Lehman Award - New York City, June 21, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2785)
- Great Neck Public Schools Taping for Retirement Dinner - Great Neck, Long Island, New York, June 24, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2786)
- Tonight Show with Johnny Carson, June 24, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2787)
- Judicial Conference Dinner - State Trial Judges, June 25, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2788)
- St. Lawrence Seaway and Power Project - Massena, New York, June 27, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2789)
  Celebration of 10th Anniversary of opening.
- St. Lawrence Seaway and Power Project - Massena, New York, June 27, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2790)
- Scope Magazine Article - Untried Answer to Our Number One Health Problem, July 17, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2791)
- Statement re: Long Island Railroad, July 23, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2792)
- Adirondack Museum - Blue Mountain Lake, New York, August 1, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2793)
  Dedication of building.
- Press Conference - Albany, New York, August 1, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2794)
- Adirondack Museum - Blue Mountain Lake, New York, August 1, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2795)
- Readers Digest Meeting with Editors - Pleasantville, New York, August 6, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2796)
- Long Island Association - Breakfast Meeting About Long Island Rail Road, August 7, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2797)
- National Legislative Conference - St. Louis, Missouri - Cancelled, August 27, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2798)
- National Legislative Conference - St. Louis, Missouri - Cancelled, August 27, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2799)
- State Fair - Syracuse, New York, August 28, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2800)
- State Fair - Syracuse, New York, August 28, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2801)
- State Fair - Syracuse, New York, August 28, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2802)
- State Farm Dinner - Syracuse, New York, August 27, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2803)
- Meet the Press - National Governor's Conference Panel, Including NAR, August 31, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2804)
- National Governors' Conference - Colorado Springs, Colorado, August 31-September 3, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2805)
- National Governors' Conference - Committee on Human Resources - Colorado Springs, Colorado, September 2, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2806)
- Mid-Hudson Industrial Association - Poughkeepsie, New York, September 5, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2807)
- Meeting with Business Community - Mid-Hudson Area, September 5, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2808)
- Polytherm Plastics Company, September 5, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2809)
  Plant tour and dedication.
- Polytherm Plastics Company, September 5, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2810)
- 195th Anniversary - Meeting of the First Continental Congress - New York City, September 5, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2811)
- International Amalgamated Transit Union - Biennial Convention, September 8, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2812)
- International Amalgamated Transit Union - Biennial Convention, September 8, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2813)
- County Officers Association - Kiamesha Lake, New York, September 9, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2814)
- County Officers Association - Kiamesha Lake, New York, September 9, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2815)
- North Central Bronx General Hospital - Ground Breaking Ceremony, September 10, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2816)
- North Central Bronx General Hospital - Ground Breaking Ceremony, September 10, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2817)
- Brooklyn Chamber of Commerce, September 11, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2818)
- Meeting with Business Community of Syracuse Area, September 16, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2819)
- Council of Appalachian Governors Meeting - Williamsburg, Virginia, September 17, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2820)
- National Press Club - Washington, DC, September 17, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2820A)
- Otsego County - Republican Picnic - Cooperstown, New York, September 18, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2820B)
- Message to Transportation Department Maintenance Employees, September 18, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2820C)
- Schoharie County Republican Committee - Howes Cove, New York, September 18, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2821)
- Associated Industries of New York State - Lake Placid, New York, September 19, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2821A)
- Intergovernmental Advisory Commission - Washington, DC, September 19, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2822)
- State-Local Bond Interest Provisions of HR 13270 - US Senate Finance Committee, September 23, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2823)
- Visit Nassau/Suffolk County Fair - Bethpage, New York, September 23, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2824)
- Meeting with Nassau County Business Community, September 23, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2825)
- New York State Conservation Council - Annual Convention Awards Dinner - Lake Placid, New York, September 25, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2826)
- Meeting with Buffalo Area Business Community, September 30, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2827)
- New York State Executive Budget - 40th Anniversary - Albany, New York, October 1, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2828)
- Nassau County Weekly Press Association Annual Dinner - Garden City, New York, October 5, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2829)
- State University of New York, Purchase - Groundbreaking Ceremony - Purchase, New York, October 6, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2830)
- White Plains Business Meeting, October 6, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2831)
- Westchester County Republican Committee - Chairman's Club Cocktail Party - White Plains, New York, October 6, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2832)
- 74th Annual Convention of the American Osteopathic Association - New York City, October 6, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2833)
- National Conference of UPI Editors and Publishers - Bermuda, October 7, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2834)
- Long Island Association - Westbury, Long Island, New York, October 7, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2835)
- Nine Mile Point Nuclear Power Plant - Dedication Ceremony - Oswego, New York, October 9, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 2836)
- Willard State Hospital - 100th Anniversary Celebration - Interlake, New York, October 9, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 2837)
- Albany County Republican Committee - Fund Raising Reception - Albany, New York, October 9, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 2838)
- Annual Columbus Day Dinner - New York City, October 11, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 2839)
- Alfred E. Smith Memorial Foundation, Inc. - Annual Dinner - Waldorf, New York, October 16, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 2840)
- Steuben County Republican Committee - Fund Raising Dinner - Corning, New York, October 17, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 2841)